friendseat.com 2018-08-17

# Privacy Policy | FriendsEAT

The privacy of our visitors to FriendsEAT.com is important to us.

At FriendsEAT.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit FriendsEAT.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

 **Log Files:**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

 **Cookies:**  
Like most websites, FriendsEAT.com uses cookies for various purposes. For registered users, we use cookies to store user id and password information. For non-registered users, we use a cookie only to identify whether you are a return visitor. Third party advertisers on the site may also place cookies on your browser. If you want disable cookies, you can usually find this information in “help” section of your browser. Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to use certain areas or features of the Site.

We also use third party advertisements on FriendsEAT.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

### Sub-processors

A sub-processor includes any 3rd party that we share personally identifiable info with.

Here is that list with what they do and their location

  * 1and1 – Registrar – USA
  * AWS – Content Host – USA
  * Automattic – CMS – USA
  * Chargify – Billing Provider – USA
  * Cloudflare – Content Delivery Network – USA
  * Google – Hosting – USA
  * Mailchimp – Email Campaigns – USA
  * PayPal – Billing Provider -USA
  * Twilio – SMS Provider – USA

### Your privacy responsibilities

To help protect your privacy, be sure:

  * not to share your user ID or password with anyone else;
  * to log off the FriendsEAT Website when you are finished;
  * to take customary precautions to guard against “malware” (viruses, Trojan horses, bots, etc.), for example by installing and updating suitable anti-virus software.

### Notice to European Union users

FriendsEAT‘s operations are located primarily in the United States. If you provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of the European Union (EU) to the United States. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described herein.

### Data Protection Agreement

If you are doing business with customers in the EU and are in need of signing our DPA please email us at us@friendseat.com to receive a link to the agreement.

### Access / Portability

A user may request access to a copy of the personal data that we have collected. Users who wish to request portability can reach out to us at any time by emailing us@friendseat.com.

### Deletion

A user has the right to request that we delete all of their personal data. Users who wish to inquire about the right to be forgotten will be able at anytime to email us at us@friendseat.com.

 **DoubleClick DART cookies:**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting: <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

 **The Way We Use Information:**  
We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.  
Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you sign-up on the website.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.  
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

 **Our Commitment To Data Security:**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. Individuals under the age of 13 are not allowed to use our site or any properties associated with FriendsEAT.com.

 **  
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online by viewing your profile for your respective account.  
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

 **  
How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at us |at| friendsEAT.com.

List of Vendors Approved:
